[
    {
      "question": "네",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "아니요",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "우리는",
      "answer": "We"
    },
    {
      "question": "오늘",
      "answer": "Today"
    },
    {
      "question": "어제",
      "answer": "Yesterday"
    },
    {
      "question": "내일",
      "answer": "Tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "밤",
      "answer": "Night"
    },
    {
      "question": "아침",
      "answer": "Morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "왜",
      "answer": "Why"
    },
    {
      "question": "언제",
      "answer": "When"
    }
  ]
  